# Judith Mulundu

4133 church street apt 24A, Clarkston, Georgia, 30021, US (470) 430-5839 judithmulundu@gmail.com

### **Professional Summary**

Engaging and upbeat personality with the ability to recruit, train, and coach new employees to help the company achieve its brand and growth goals.

Encourages open communication with employees and provides feedback to help them perform better at work.

Ability to use sound judgment and independent decision-making skills to positively impact company success.

[Recruiter] with experience in payroll, recruitment, and training. A beginner web developer.

#### Skills

- Team collaboration
- Faster learning
- Active listening and attentiveness

**General Skills**: Customer Service, External Communication, Adaptability, Problem-solving,

- Math skills
- Multiple languages: English, French, Swahili and Lingala.

Time Management, Attention to Detail, Leadership

#### Education

Business Management - Associate of Science Interactive College Of Technology - Atlanta - Chamblee, GA

Life Insurance - Life insurance Agent - 2022 XCEL Solutions - online course

Law Enforcement Administration - Bachelor of Science - 2016 William Booth University - Kinshasa, DRC

**High School** - 2011 **Afrika College** - Kinshasa, Democratic Republic of the Congo

## **Work History**

**Assistant manager** - July, 2022 to Present **Tekton Career Training** - Clarkston, GA

Recuiter specialist - July, 2022 to Present Diversity insight staffing - Clarkston, GA

Food service - February, 2022 to May, 2022 Bon appetit - Atlanta, GA

Intern Attorney - April, 2016 to August, 2016 Matete's Court - Kinshasa, Kinshasa